{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Q1. What is the capital of France?",
      "options": ["Paris", "London", "Berlin", "Madrid"],
      "answer": "Paris"
    },
    {
      "question": "Q2. Which planet is known as the Red Planet?",
      "options": ["Earth", "Mars", "Jupiter", "Saturn"],
      "answer": "Mars"
    },
    {
      "question": "Q3. Which one of the following river flows between Vindhyan and Satpura ranges?",
      "options": ["Narmada", "Mahanadi", "Son", "Netravati"],
      "answer": "Narmada"
    },
    {
      "question": "Q4. The Central Rice Research Station is situated in?",
      "options": ["Chennai", "Cuttack", "Bangalore", "Quilon"],
      "answer": "Cuttack"
    },
    {
      "question": "Q5. Who among the following wrote Sanskrit grammar?",
      "options": ["Kalidasa", "Charak", "Panini", "Aryabhatt"],
      "answer": "Panini"
    },
    {
      "question": "Q6. Which among the following headstreams meets the Ganges in last?",
      "options": ["Alaknanda", "Pindar", "Mandakini", "Bhagirathi"],
      "answer": "Bhagirathi"
    },
    {
      "question": "Q7. The metal whose salts are sensitive to light is?",
      "options": ["Zinc", "Silver", "Copper", "Aluminum"],
      "answer": "Silver"
    },
    {
      "question": "Q8. Patanjali is well known for the compilation of â€“",
      "options": ["Yoga Sutra", "Panchatantra", "Brahma Sutra", "Ayurveda"],
      "answer": "Yoga Sutra"
    },
    {
      "question": "Q9. Which one of the following rivers originates in Brahmagiri range of Western Ghats?",
      "options": ["Pennar", "Cauvery", "Krishna", "Tapti"],
      "answer": "Cauvery"
    },
    {
      "question": "Q10. The country that has the highest in Barley Production?",
      "options": ["China", "India", "Russia", "France"],
      "answer": "Russia"
    }

  ]
}
